ANDREW CLARK

9 The Hollows, Giffnock, Glasgow, G46 7JB andrewwclark@me.com · 07772 166553

A motivated, hardworking and enthusiastic 4th year Mechanical Engineering with Aeronautics student at the University of Glasgow. Possesses an excellent work ethic with a goal to gain valuable experience with a reputable company to build a successful career in the Engineering industry.

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2017- PRESENT

MECHANICAL ENGINEERING WITH AERONAUTICS MENG, THE UNIVERSITY OF GLASGOW

- Currently in fourth year working towards a Master of Engineering Degree in Mechanical Engineering with Aeronautics.
- Built a solid knowledge base and understanding in Mechanical Engineering, Thermodynamics, Aeronautics and stress analysis, and gained excellent team working and communication skills through group projects.

Grades (GPA): (1st class = 18+, Maximum = 22)

- 2019-2020: 21.74
- 2018-2019: 21.65
- 2017-2018: 20.44

Awards:

• Engineering excellent list for academic performance - awarded 3 years consecutively throughout studies (2017/2018, 2018/2019 & 2019-2020).

2010-2017

A-LEVEL AND GCSE, REIGATE GRAMMAR SCHOOL

A-level:

- Maths A
- Physics A
- Business B

AS-Level:

• Chemistry A

GCSE:

- A*: Maths, Physics, Product Design, Chemistry, Biology, Geography
- A: English Language, English Literature, History, French

Roles and Achievements:

- Awarded the Business prize for 2017
- Sixth form Prefect Acted as a role model for all students and an ambassador for the school with weekly duties.
- Mentor for new students to the school
- Bronze Award Duke of Edinburgh

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2019 - PRESENT

RECEPTIONIST, LOGISTICS ASSISTANT AND DRIVER, HARWOODS GROUP

- Employed by Harwoods Group, primarily based at their flagship Jaguar Land Rover dealership in Crawley. Duties include:
 - o **Receptionist/Showroom host** Responsible as the first point of contact for customers, both face to face in the dealership and assisting with enquiries over the phone.

 Logistics assistant and Driver - Responsible for arranging and implementing timely movement of cars between the group's dealerships, in addition to both Sales and Service driving. The role also involved keen attention to detail to inspect and accurately record deliveries into the dealership.

AUGUST 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

PARTS ADVISOR, HARWOODS GROUP

- Employed in the parts department at Harwoods Group's Audi dealership in Southampton.
 - Revamped the department and reorganised all the parts stored on site, in order to prepare for an external audit.
 - o Arranged the parts which would be required the next day and delivered parts by van to another workshop.
- The role required excellent attention to detail and organisational skills, as well as the ability to multitask and prioritise tasks while working towards strict deadlines.

AUGUST 2015 - MARCH 2016

SALES ASSISTANT, WM MORRISON SUPERMARKETS PLC

- Assigned to the beers, wines and spirits section typically working 20 hours a week after school and on Saturdays. Duties included:
 - Ensuring sufficient stock on shelves, cleaning, and assisting customers with finding items and any other queries; always ensuring the highest level of customer service.
- The role required high attention to detail and reliability due to the department being short-staffed.

JUNE 2015 – OCTOBER 2015

NEWSPAPER DELIVERY, SRISAI NEWS REIGATE

- Newspaper delivery by bicycle 6 days a week before school and on Saturday mornings.
- This role required a high level of reliability and a strong work ethic to ensure timely deliveries and customer satisfaction.

SKILLS

- Strong teamworking and communication
- Ability to work under pressure
- Adaptability to different situations and roles
- Good working knowledge of Microsoft office, particularly Excel
- Time management and prioritisation
- Organisation and attention to detail
- Very competent in Solidworks Computer Aided Design software
- Competent in MATLAB software

INTERESTS AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Current affairs, Snooker, Cycling and General fitness
- Full valid UK driving license and car

REFERENCES

- Patrick Lake (Head of Business, Crawley Jaguar Land-Rover): pjlake@btinternet.com
- Martin Clothier (Parts Manager, Southampton Audi): martin.clothier@harwoods.uk.com